{"data":[{"question":"Wendy ___ one day to decide whether she should reject the offer.","a":"was given","b":"gave","c":"had given","d":"was giving","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple past tense- passive voice: was\/were + PP","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Tim ___ while he ___ his motorcycle and hurt himself.","a":"fell, were riding","b":"fell, was riding","c":"had fallen, was riding","d":"had fallen, rode","answer":"2","explain":"\n-Use the Past Continuous to indicate that a longer action in the past was interrupted. The interruption is usually a shorter action in the Simple Past. \n+First blank: Simple past tense\n+Second blank: simple past continuous tense","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Henry was disappointed that most of the guests ___ when he ___ at the party.","a":"left, arrived","b":"left, had arrived","c":"had left, arrived","d":"had left, had arrived","answer":"3","explain":"\n- The Past Perfect expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past. \n+ Past Perfect, when simple past tense","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"The police found that the office ___ and a lot of valuables ___.","a":"had broken into , had been stolen","b":"has broken into, has been stolen","c":"had been broken into, were stolen","d":"has been broken into, were stolen","answer":"3","explain":"\n- First blank: Past perfect tense (The Past Perfect expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past (found). + passive voice \n- Second blank: Simple past tense + passive voice","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"The new-comer is supposed to report to the director as soon as he ___.","a":"arrives","b":"will arrive","c":"is arriving","d":"is going to arrive","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple present tense \n+ Future tense (\"is supposed to report\" implies action will happen in future)+ as soon as simple present tense ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Where ___ the gift certificate? I can't see it anywhere. \"It ___ right here. But now it's gone.\"","a":"have you put, was put","b":"did you put, has been put","c":"were you putting, has been put","d":"had you put, was being put","answer":"1","explain":"\n+First blank:  Present perfect tense\n+Second blank: simple past  tense + passive voice","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Hello! I ___ you ___ in Taipei. How long have you been here?","a":"hadn't known, are","b":"don't know, were","c":"didn't know, were","d":"haven't known, are","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Verb agreement: past perfect tense- simple past; simple past tense- simple past tense; present tense- present tense\/future tense.... ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"When ___ again? \"When she _________, I'll let you know.\"","a":"will Mary come, will come","b":"Mary comes, comes","c":"will Mary come, comes","d":"Mary comes, will come","answer":"3","explain":"\n- First blank: Simple future tense\n- Second blank: Simple present tense\n+Future tense + when simple present tense","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"No permission has ___ for anyone to enter the area.","a":"given","b":"been given","c":"be giving","d":"to give","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Present perfect tense - passive voice: have\/has been +pp","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Those salesmen asked me to have a drink with them. I said that it was at least five years since I ___ a good drink.","a":"was enjoying","b":"had enjoyed","c":"had been enjoying","d":"enjoyed","answer":"2","explain":"- We use past perfect continuous","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"}]}